(Raj:)seemed like a chance
to show off.
There he is!
(Raj:)There's my happy
Hebraic homeboy.
(Raj:)Yeah, that's the smile
I'm gonna remember
(Raj:)when you're living in the desert
and I'm living with your wife.
(Beverley:)So, what do you do for a living?
(Randall:)Mommy, you want
to take this one?
(Susan:)Um, Randall's
in between jobs.
(Randall:)And court appearances.
(Wyatt:)It's nice to meet the woman
(Wyatt:)who raised this fine young man.
(Wyatt:)I'm looking forward
to meeting his father.
(Beverley:)Prepare to be disappointed.
(Leonard:)And he can't wait
to meet you, too.
(Leonard:)Can I get anyone a drink?
(Wyatt:)Well, I could use
another beer.
(Susan:)You're done.
(Susan:)He's done.
Hey! Is everyone getting
to know each other?
Not at all!